Guide to the Stanford University, School of Humanities and Sciences, Innovative Academic Courses, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, School of Humanities and Sciences, Innovative Academic Courses, records
1966-1992
SC0431
Stanford University. School of Humanities and Sciences. Innovative Academic Courses.
105 Linear feet (56 boxes)
The records include catalogs; course files, proposals, evaluations, and readers; minutes of policy board meetings; correspondence, budgets, and other administrative files; posters, audio tapes, and video tapes; and clippings pertaining to courses offered through IAC, especially the SWOPSI and UGS programs. Also included are files of IAC's last director, Margo Horn; also represented in the records is Carolyn Lougee, Dean of Humanities and Sciences.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
The records were received by the Stanford University Archives via administrative transfers, 1992-1995 and 2006.
Information about Access
The collection is open for use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Innovative Academic Courses (IAC) was instituted in the fall of 1985 to administer three existing alternative academic programs: SWOPSI, Stanford Workshops on Political and Social Issues, UGS, Undergraduate Special Courses, and Freshman-Sophomore Seminars. SWOPSI courses, first offered in 1969, emphasized student participation and group collaboration through academic study, small-group discussion, and community involvement. UGS courses, first offered in 1966, provided a setting for teaching new or interdisciplinary methods and subjects not otherwise available at the University. Freshman-Sophomore Seminars provided communication between faculty in the professional schools and first and second year students through seminars focusing on scholarly research. IAC was discontinued at the end of the 1991-1992 academic year.
Description of the Collection
The records include catalogs; course files, proposals, evaluations, and readers; minutes of policy board meetings; correspondence, budgets, and other administrative files; posters, audio tapes, and video tapes; and clippings pertaining to courses offered through IAC, especially the SWOPSI and UGS programs. Includes files of IAC's last director, Margo Horn; also represented in the records is Carolyn Lougee, Dean of Humanities and Sciences.
Access Terms
Faulkner, P.; Horn, Margo.; Lougee, Carolyn C., 1942-; Stanford University. School of Humanities and Sciences. Innovative Academic Courses.; Stanford University; Stanford Workshops on Political and Social Issues.; Educational innovations.; Interdisciplinary approach in education.; Phonotapes.; Posters.; Universities and colleges--Curricula.; Videorecordings.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-1992-086
  - UGS Catalogs 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - UGS Catalogs 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - UGS Catalogs 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - UGS Catalogs Fall 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - UGS Catalogs Winter 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - UGS Catalogs Fall 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - UGS Catalogs Winter 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - UGS Catalogs Spring 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - UGS Catalogs Fall 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - UGS Catalogs Winter 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - UGS Catalogs Spring 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - UGS Catalogs Fall 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - UGS Catalogs Winter 1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - UGS Catalogs Spring 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - UGS Catalogs Fall 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - UGS Catalogs Winter 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - UGS Catalogs Spring 1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - UGS Catalogs Fall 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - UGS Catalogs Winter 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - UGS Catalogs Spring 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - UGS Catalogs Fall 1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - UGS Catalogs Winter 1983 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - UGS Catalogs Spring 1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - UGS Catalogs Fall 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - UGS Catalogs Winter 1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - UGS Catalogs Spring 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - UGS Catalogs Autumn 1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - UGS Catalogs Winter 1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - UGS Catalogs Spring 1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - US134 Environmental Impact on Health, Winter 1969 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - US175 Computers and Privacy, Fall 1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - US179 Logging Policy, Fall 1969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - US182 Scientists and Decision Making (Technological Issues), Winter 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Spring Quarter General 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - US115 The New Education, Spring 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - US178 Air Pollution in the Bay Area, Spring 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Fall Quarter General 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - US142 Bay Area Environmental Impact on Health, Fall 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - US146 Micronesia, Fall 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Winter Quarter General 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Spring Quarter General 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Spring 1970-1971, 1 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - SWOP 120B Volunteer Work with Severly Distubed Children, Winter 1976 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses, Spring 1970-1971, 2 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses, Spring 1970-1971, 3 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Autumn Quarter 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Problems of International Enviormental Disruption 1972 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Winter Quarter (2B-160) 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Spring Quarter 1971-1972, courses 2C-43 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Spring Quarter 1971-1972, courses 44-126C (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Autumn Quarter 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Winter 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Spring Quarter, #3-38, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Spring Quarter, #39-124, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Autumn Quarter 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Winter Quarter #004-038, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Winter Quarter #32-114, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Spring Quarter 1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Autumn Quarter 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Winter Quarter 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Winter Quarter 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Autumn Quarter 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Spring Quarter 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Winter Quarter 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Autumn Quarter 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Spring Quarter 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Autumn, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses Spring 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses, Spring 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses, Autumn Winter 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses, Spring 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Special Courses, Autumn Winter 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - US11 Philosophy of Women (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - US 20 Symphony Winter 1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - US8 Zionism and Arab Nationalism Fall 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - US 10 University Governance and Administrative Process- Fall 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - US 25 Phil. and Social Science Approaches to Sex Roles Winter 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 4A Problems of Chronic Illness and Disease in Children Spring 1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - US12 Shakespeare's Sonnets Spring 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - US18 Marxist Perpectives on School and Society, Winter 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - US 21, Rising Son: Soc. Constraints on Development of Conciousness, Schartz, Sam, Winter 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - U S22 Feminist Theory, Winter 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - US 26 Women and the Law Winter 1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - US 27 Naturalist Literature (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - US 5 Political Ideas of Emerson, Thoreau, Whitman Spring 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - US 13 Comedy and the Heroic Spring 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - US1 5 Intro. to Music Appreciation, Spring 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Women in Shakespeare Spring 1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - US 25 Libertarianism, Spring 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - US116 Issues in Science and Religion Spring 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - US 8 Technology and Broadcast Programming Mid-Quarter and End-Quarter Evaluations, Autumn 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - US 9 Androgyny and Feminism Mid-Quarter and End-Quarter Evaluations, Fall, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - US11 Intro. to NA Studies Mid-Quarter and End-Quarter Evaluations, Autumn 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - US 21 Issues of Nuclear Power, Winter 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - US 20 Contraceptive Counseling Spring 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - US 19 People History- Mike Thurman Spring 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - US 38 Comic Genius of Evelyn Waugh, Sue Saffle, Spring 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - US 4 Fighting Theory: Kinesiology, Jerry Robinson, Winter 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - US 9 Plays as Theatre (Hokanson) Spring 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - US 15 Tolkien (Art Coleman) Spring 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - US 23 Who do Men Say that I am? Jesus, Spring 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - US 7 Geology of the Grand Canyon, Autumn 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - US 3 Exercise and Nutrition, Winter 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - US 11 Critical Examination of the Writing Prob- Zorn- Winter 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - US 2 Yoga and the Mind, Cousins and Pickar- Autumn 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - US 14 John Roos Debate, Autumn 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - US 24 Intelligent Speculations: Options and Other Beasts, Autumn 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - US 26 Celestial Naviagation Fred Levien- Autumn 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - US 20: Understanding the Literary Crisis, Jeff Zorn, Winter 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - US 102 Risk and Insurance, Oscar Serbian, Winter 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - US 16B Adanced Speech, Marc Zafferano, Winter 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - US 5 Whitman Colloquium Autumn 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - US 7 Grand Canyon, Winter 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - US 37 Stock Market, Autumn 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - US 20: Phil Issues ED, Winter 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - US 24 Stock Options, Winter 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - US 19 Amateur Radio, Spring 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - US 18 World Citizenship George Duca, Autumn 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - US 3: Real World Computing John Halamka, Autumn 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - US 5 Intro. to Real Estate Bonbright and Conley, Autumn 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - UGS11 Contemporary Soviety Culture, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - US 14A: Debate, Autumn 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - US 16A Practical Speech Comm., Wagstaffe, Autumn 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - US 44, Spring 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - UGS Intro. Jewish Thought and Prac. Fall 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - UGS Folklore as Literature, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - UGS Aristotle Scoledes, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - UGS President 60-80, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - UGS Making of Presidents, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - UGS 2 Ecnomic ISSUES: Evaluations, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - UGS Beginning Mandarin Conversation, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - UGS Frank Lloyd Wright, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - UGS Problems in the US-Mexico Relations, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - UGS Am. Foreign Policy in Mid. East, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - UGS Naked Eye Astronomy, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - UGS The Unseen America, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - UGS The Mythic Hero, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - UGS 37, The Stock Market Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - UGS History of Word Games, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - UGS History of Women in Art, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - UGS Contemporary Issues in Economics, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - UGS Women in Shakespeare, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - UGS Optimal Human Performance, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - UGS 116, Issues in Science and Religion, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - UGS Practical Speech Communication, Spring/ Summer 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - UGS Comparative Spirituality, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - UGS American Film, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - US16A Undergraduate Special Program Jim Wagstaffe, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - UGS 16A Practical Speech: Evaluations, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - UGS 38 Unseen America:Evaluations, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - UGS 8, Basic Criminal Law, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - UGS 10, Alzheimers Disease Project, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - UGS 11 A/B Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - UGS 13, Introduction to the Nuclear Era, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - UGS11B Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Dennis Matthies, Otero (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - UGS 5, German Women Writers of the 20th Century, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - UGS 7A Beginning Mandarin Conversation, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - UGS 14, Agumentation, Logic and Debate, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - UGS 18, Meaning in Music, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - UGS 23, Socio-Economic Devt. in Latin America, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - UGS 26, Poetry in Revolution, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - UGS 7B Beginning Mandarin Conversation, Spring 1985-1985 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - UGS 11A/B Working with Disturbed Children, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - UGS 16: Practical Speech Communication Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - UGS 27, Decade of Activism, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - UGS 24, Criminal Procedure, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - UGS 29 Victorian Women Writers, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - UGS 31, Trading Stock Options, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - UGS 32, Classic Hollywood Filsm: Masculine and Feminine Images, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - UGS (34)001 Photojournalism, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - UGS 35, Personal Health, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - UGS 36, Street Theater and Brecht, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - UGS 37, Stock Market, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - UGS 38, Gambeling, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - UGS 39, The Writer of Essays as Critic, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - UGS 40: The Philosophy of Liebnitz, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - UGS 41, Vietnam, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - UGS 42, An Inductive Study of Mark, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - UGS 43: Feminist Utopias Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - UGS 44, Naked Eye Astronomy, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - UGS 46, Contemp. Economic Issues, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - UGS 47, Technology and the Future, (1 unit: Cedro), Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - UGS 48: Race, Class and Sex in Novels by Black Women Writers, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - UGS 45, Traditional Chinese vs. Western Healing in Urban Taiwan, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - UGS 49: Intro. to Ethical Decision-Making, Nazi Rise to Power, Spring 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - UGS 001, Photojournalism, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - UGS 002, A & B Disturbed Children, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - UGS 003: Vietnam, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - UGS 005, Practical Speech, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - UGS 6, Caribbean Poetry, (1 unit) Fall 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - UGS 10, Law in Socialist Countries, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - UGS 22, Analysing Classic Movies, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - UGS 23, Intro. to the Nuclear Era, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - UGS 24, Street Theatre und Brecht, (1 unit) Fall 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - UGS 1 Photojournalism and the Art of Documentary, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - UGS 004: Women of North Africa, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - UGS 007, Theatrical Dance, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - UGS 20, Vienna, Theater and Culture, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - UGS 008, American Jewish Women Writers, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - UGS 010, The US Legal System, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - UGS 026, Greece and Turkey, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - UGS 028, Photojournalism and the Art of Documentary, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - UGS 060: Solar Car Project, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - UGS 9, Literature of the Gay Male Experience, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - UGS 16A Practical Speech Communication Spring 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - UGS 21 Perspectives on the Arts, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - UGS 27, American Foreign Policy in the Middle East, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - UGS21 Contemporary Mid. East: Problems for American Foreign Policy, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - UGS33, Sports Psychology, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - UGS28, Issues of Central America, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - UGS29: Poland in Contemporary Times, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - UGS30, Rock Music in the 60's, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - UGS31, Women in Myth and Prehistory, Spring, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - UGS32, Critical Thinking and the Media, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - UGS016: (A & B) 018: Practical Speech Communication, Summer 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - UGS5 Genesis, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - UGS027 Prof. Thatcher, Part I, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - UGS027 Prof. Thatcher, Part II, Winter 1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - UGS 27 Political Dynamics of the Middle East Winter 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - UGS 34 The Theory and Practice of Games, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - UGS35 Eureka! The Literature of California, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - UGS36 Poltical Theories of Sexuality, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - UGS37 The Nazi Period: Moral Dilemmas: Winter 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - UGS38 Continuous Pattern and Surface Design, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - UGS39 Poles and Jews: History and Controversy: Winter 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - UGS40 Persian Gulf: Opportunity for Disaster Winter 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - UGS15 Socially Responsible Investing, Fall 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - UGS 3 Vietnam: The American Experience, Fall 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - UGS12 International Dance Theater: Political Performance Art, Fall 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - UGS041 Theater of Protest: Social Rebellion, Spring 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - UGS042, Hitchcock Al Jacobs Spring 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - UGS042 The Films of Hitchcock: Spring 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - UGS043 Women and Political Terror... Spring 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - UGS44 Image Making and Memory, Spring 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - UGS45 Sexual Identity and Literature, Spring 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - UGS46 Greece and Turkey Spring 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - UGS47 Controversial Issues at Stanford, Spring 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - UGS48 Pleasure, Pain and Power, Spring 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - UGS49 Women, Men and Patriarchy, Spring 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - UGS50 Sociology of Culture: Societ. Influence... Spring 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - UGS003: Vietnam- The American Experience Fall 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - UGS061: Islamic History: The Early Period, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - UGS062: Language, Gender and Communication, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - UGS 062, Leslie H. Townsend, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - UGS045, Carlston/Garber (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - UGS066: Communities and Utopia, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - UGS 063: Innovative Cancer Therapies, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - UGS065: Growing Up Female: Cross Cultural Portrayals, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - UGS 001 Chicano Immigrant History Winter 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - UGS071 Everyday Life in Shakespeare's Age, Winter 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - UGS074: The Female Nude in Ren. Art, Winter 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - UGS077: Hollywood from DW to RR, Winter 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - UGS080: Islamic Fundamentalism Winter 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - UGS 083: The Nazi Period Winter 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - UGS086: The Politics of Poetry, Winter 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - UGS86, Professor Linda Garber (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - UGS11: American Violence: Guns, Spring 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - UGS015: Alternative Press Spring 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - UGS019: Informatics and Third World Development Spring 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - UGS017: Hindu Mythology Spring 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - UGS 023: Medical Models: Wellness Spring 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - UGS029: Puerto Rico: American Colonialism Spring 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - UGS034: South African Image in the USA Spring 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - UGS026: Principles and Practice in the Amer. Conservative Mvment: Spring 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - UGS 38: Women's Literature of the Holocaust: Spring 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - UGS036: Voices from the Grassroots Social Movements in India, Spring 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - UGS 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Specials 127 Fall 1970 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - UGS 160 B Sleep and Dreams (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Special 138 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - UGS 094, Lee Antz, Nicuraga and Revolution (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Science Fiction, Tad Williams, UGS 90, Fall 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Withdrawn or Rejected 1968-1969, Undergrad Special Courses (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Rejected Fall 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Fall Evaluation 1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rejected Winter 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Discontinued Winter 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Rejected Proposals Winter Quarter 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Rejected Spring 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Rejected for Fall 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Rejected for Fall 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Rejected Proposals Fall 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Rejected Winter Quarter 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Rejected for Spring Quarter 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Rejected for Fall Quarter 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Rejected for Winter 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Unsuccessful Fall 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Evaluations Alben, Alex 1979 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Davis, Angela (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Photojournalism Domingo Aviado (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Baker, Andy (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Beach, Robert (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Evaluations Biller, Janet 1975 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Boothe, Tom (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Bosley, David (Box 7, Folder 29)